

Elena Gjorgijovski

OFFICE MANAGER

Details

Novosadska 27 Bitola, 7000 North Macedonia 076491500

mitrovik.elena@gmail.com

NATIONALIT'

Macedonian

DRIVING LICENSE

В

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

02-06-1994 Bitola

Links

Linkedin Profile

Skills

Decision Making

Creativity

Computer Skills

Critical thinking and problem solving

Interpersonal Skills

Adaptability

Ability to Multitask

Customer Service

Effective Time Management

Microsoft Office

Communication Skills

Fast Learner

Profile

As a dedicated and results-driven professional, I bring a unique set of skills to the role of Office Manager. With my first work experience as a Assistant Marketing Manager, I have developed a strong attention to detail, excellent organizational skills, and the ability to work collaboratively with a team. In my previous roles, I have proven my ability to manage multiple tasks, prioritize effectively, and ensure that all office operations run smoothly. With a commitment to professionalism and a passion for creating a positive work environment, I am confident in my ability to contribute to the success of your organization as an Office Manager.

Employment History

Floor manager, Spring Creek Ranch, Jackson Hole, WY, USA

JUNE 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2014

- · Presentation of arrangements
- Serving
- · Training employees
- Hosting,
- · Developing floor plans for a events.
- · Coordination of employees
- · Overseeing employees

Floor manager, The Kitchen Restaurant, Jackson Hole, WY, USA

JUNE 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2015

- · Conducting schedules for employees,
- · presentation of arrangements,
- Serving
- Hosting
- · Developing floor plans for a events.
- · Coordinating employees
- Training employees

Assistant Marketing Manager, CEHTMedical, Skopje

EPTEMBER 2015 - DECEMBER 2016

- Coordinated mailings, marketing materials, and website content.
- Assisted in the creation of graphic materials for the use of the marketing department.
- Organized and analyzed data and marketing results.
- · Organization and maintenance of mailing and shipping
- Organization and scheduling travel arrangements.
- · Organization of office operations and events.
- · Coordination with departments on all office equipment.
- · Archive work;
- Collaboration with the other departments (finance, marketing, HR) for ongoing activities and related tasks

Medical representative, CEHTMedical, Skopje, N. Macedonia

NOVEMBER 2015 - NOVEMBER 2016

- Market research
- · Develop marketing plan
- Product presentations
- · Designing Promo materials
- Writing Product Manuals
- Translations Product ManualsMaking price quotation

Google Docs Business Communications Effective Time Management Team Worker Digital marketing tool

Copywriting and Story writing

Search Engine Optimization

Meta Tag Optimization

Strategic planning

Google analitycs

ahrefs Webmaster Tool

Screaming Frog SEO Spider Tool

Hobbies

Snow Boarding, Hiking Bicycle Riding CrossFit Training

Languages

Macedonian

English

Serbian

- · Keeping warehouse quantity records
- · Administrative work
- Owner assistant
- · Worked well with nurses, doctors, and medical professionals.

Medical coder, Taskforce BPO, Bitola

DECEMBER 2016 - JULY 2018

- · Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner
- · Demonstrated a strong understanding of positive HR practices.
- Operated with a willingness to embrace chance and adapt strategies accordingly.
- Remained proactive and constantly took initiative to achieve desired outcomes.
- · Consistently communicated in a lucid and effective manner.
- Brought forth empathy and a constant consideration of the perspective of colleagues and business partners.
- · Coding efficiently while training new employees

Medical scriber, VRS/ Campbell, Cunningham, Haun ophthalmology clinic, Knoxville, Tennessee

JULY 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- · Trained medical ophthalmology scribe
- · Live scribing
- · Communicating with patients of different ages and different cultures
- · Finishing on time and with efficiency
- Fast typing while listening the visit of the patient in the clinic with the doctor present
- Team work

Medical biller, VRS/ Taskforce BPO, Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2018 - JULY 2021

- Financial processing
- Posting
- Coding office visits of patients
- · Coding and billing specialist retina visits
- · Billing optical visits,
- · Billing specialist retina visits
- Billing ophthalmology surgeries
- · Posting payments, claims and denials
- Communicating with insurance companies and
- · Collaborating with collages from USA

SEO Specialist, AVTechnologies, Bitola

JANUARY 2022 - FEBRUARY 2023

- Create detailed formats and content briefs with clear instructions for both writers and
- · editors;
- Do keyword research with a focus on topic research to create clusters for websites:
- · Understand and monitor competitors' strategies;
- · Develop effective interlinking strategies;
- Review content produced by the team to ensure that it meets quality standards, it is
- · factually accurate and it is optimized for search engines.

- Keeping up to date with changes to search algorithms and industry best practices and
- · adapting SEO strategies accordingly.
- Track and analyze website metrics with the help of Google Analytics, Google Search
- · Console, Ahrefs, SerpRobot, Screaming Frog, etc.

Social Media Specialist, AVTechnologies, Bitola

MAY 2022 - FEBRUARY 2023

- Developed and implemented social media strategies
- Managed daily activity on social media platforms (Instagram, Pinterest, Linkedin)
- · Produced original social media content
- · Increased the number of followers on Instagram and Pinterest
- · Responsible for social media strategy and content for 2 profiles
- · Research target audience and discover current trends
- Using tactical offers/the promotion of relevant products to help drive online orders
- Supporting the online media campaigns of the company in any way possible
- Collaborate with other departments (customer relations, sales etc.) to manage reputation
- · Created weekly reports through advanced Excel skills
- · Created weekly and monthly google analytics reports
- · Used Canva to create visualizations designs
- · Recorded data regarding website traffic and user feedback.
- · Partnered with marketing teams to maximize the power of social media.
- · Brought forth a self-motivated and passionate attitude.
- · Sourced and managed relationships with social media partners.

Education

High school, Josip Broz Tito, Bitola

SEPTEMBER 2008 - MAY 2012

Undergraduate studies, University American College Skopje, Skopje

SEPTEMBER 2012 - MAY 2015

Bachelor of Business Administration

Master studies, University American College Skopje, Skopje

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JULY 2016

Operational Management and Business Administration

Courses

MedicalCoding, TaskforceBPO Academy

DECEMBER 2016 - APRIL 2017

References

Andriana Moskovska from AVTechnologies

ane_bt@live.com